{
    "id": "a6dc2a613f164b5aae847ff83dbf7a91",
    "title": "Future tense quiz",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "87453b6757b645ae93977075e68172d9",
            "title": "Future Tense Quiz",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The train ……………….. at 6 pm.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "leaves",
                        "will leave",
                        "would leave"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will phone you when I ………………….. time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will have",
                        "have",
                        "would have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………………… my grandparents this evening.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "visit",
                        "will visit",
                        "am visiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Look at the sky. It ……………………. to rain.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will go",
                        "goes",
                        "is going"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Perhaps we ………………….. Paris next month.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "visit",
                        "will visit",
                        "are visiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Unless we ……………………. now we can’t be there on time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "start",
                        "will start",
                        "started"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The next term ………………….. on September 15th.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "begin",
                        "begins",
                        "will begin"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Oh dear! I ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will sneeze",
                        "sneeze",
                        "am going to sneeze"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am sure he ……………………. win.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "will be"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ……………………. you one of these days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "are seeing",
                        "will be seeing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}